kmfusa.com 2016-10-29

# Privacy Policy

## Kia Motors Finance (KMF) Privacy Statement Highlights

Privacy and consumer trust is very important to us at Kia Motors Finance. This Privacy Statement ("Statement") applies to the Kia Motors Finance Website (the "Site"), which is owned or controlled by Kia Motors Finance (the trade name of Hyundai Capital America, a California corporation), although software, hosting and other functions and content may be provided by third parties. Throughout the Site, the terms "we," "us" and "our" refer to Kia Motors Finance. This Statement describes the types of information that Kia Motors Finance collects from visitors to the Site, what we do with this information, with whom we share this information, and how visitors can update the information they provide on the Site. This Statement also applies to any other web sites or information provided to the Kia Motors Finance by any other means (such as email or offline activities). 

While information is critical to providing quality service, we recognize that one of our most important assets is our customers' trust. Our goal is to protect your information. 

**Collection of Personal Information** **:** __

  1. • The personal information that we collect depends on the products and services you have with us.
  2. • The information we collect may be combined with information obtained from affiliates and non-affiliates.
  3. • We use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our Site and services to offer a personalized experience.

**Your Choices:**

  1. • To make proactive choices about how we communicate with you by e-mail, telephone and postal mail, follow the instructions listed in the Marketing Choices section of the full privacy policy.
  2. • To update your personal information, go to the Accuracy of Your Information section of the full privacy policy.

To limit our ability to share your personal information with affiliates regarding your credit worthiness or marketing or with non-affiliates follow the instructions listed in the Privacy Choices section of the full privacy policy. 

**Use of Personal Information** **:** __

We use the information we collect to provide the products and services you request. 

We use your information to inform you of other products or services offered by us and our affiliates. 

We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists to third parties. In order to help provide our services to you, we occasionally provide information to other companies that work on our behalf. 

Kia Motors Finance Full Privacy Policy  ****

How to Contact Us

Call toll-free (866) 331-5632 

**Full Privacy Policy**

  1. 1.General Privacy Statement 
  2. 2.Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information
  3. 3.Use and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information
  4. 4.Normal Website Usage and Cookies
  5. 5.Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)
  6. 6.Log Files
  7. 7.Do Not Track Signals
  8. 8.Your Privacy Choices
  9. 9.Your Marketing Choices
  10. 10.Accuracy of Your Information
  11. 11.Confidentiality, Security, and Data Retention
  12. 12.Children's Privacy
  13. 13.Your California Privacy Rights
  14. 14.Your Vermont Privacy Rights
  15. 15.Changes to Our Privacy Policy
  16. 16.How to Contact Us

**1\. General Privacy Statement**

Privacy and consumer trust is very important to us at Kia Motors Finance. This Privacy Statement ("Statement") applies to Kia Motors Finance Website (the "Site"), which is owned or controlled by Kia Motors Finance (the trade name of Hyundai Capital America, a California corporation), although software, hosting and other functions and content may be provided by third parties. Throughout the Site, the terms "we," "us" and "our" refer to Kia Motors Finance. This Statement describes the types of information that Kia Motors Finance collects from visitors to the Site, what we do with this information, with whom we share this information, and how visitors can update the information they provide on the Site. This Statement also applies to any other web sites or information provided to the Kia Motors Finance by any other means (such as email or offline activities). 

While information is critical to providing quality service, we recognize that one of our most important assets is our customers' trust. Our goal is to protect your information. 

**2\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

We may collect the following types of personally identifiable information about you: 

  1. a. Information we receive from you on applications for credit or other forms, such as your contact information, assets and income; and
  2. b. Information that is required for you to register and log in for your Online Account, such as your account number, e-mail address, vehicle identification number, Social Security Number, and zip code; and
  3. c. Information we receive from you about your transactions with us, or from affiliates (as permitted by law), or others such as account balances, payment history or account activity.
  4. d. Information to provide correspondence (e.g., promotions and mailed brochures) such as your name and address.
  5. e. Information from non-affiliates (as authorized by you) to enable us to complete your transactions.

**3\. Use and Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**

If you are our customer, we may use and/or disclose all of the information that we collect from you and former customers, as described below. 

  1. a. _Customer Data_

To the extent permitted by law and in accordance the [ Download Kia Motors Finance Customer Privacy Notice](https://pfile.hcamerica.com/content/dam/hca/kmf/img/privacy-policy/2016-kmf-na-na-privacy_policy-pdf.PDF), the personally identifiable information we collect about you may be shared with our affiliates and non-affiliates as follows: 

    1. I. Affiliates - Our affiliates include companies with a Kia name (except dealers); and nonfinancial companies such as Kia Motors America.

    2. II. Non-affiliates - We share with can include dealers, insurance companies, banks and other lenders, and direct marketers, including retailers.

    3. III. Joint Marketing - Companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or for other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements, such as insurance companies, credit card companies, and other financial service companies.

This information is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data and used to fulfill your request. 

We do not disclose personally identifiable information about you from your credit application or any credit reporting agencies, except as permitted by law. 

  2. b. _No Sale of Data_

We do not sell the data we collect from you, regardless of whether or not you are our customer. 

  3. c. _Disclosure Required by Law_

We will share data we collect from or about you as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process. 

**4\. Normal Website Usage and Cookies**

You can visit our Site to read about product, investment, and company information, or use some of our online tools (e.g., Which Vehicles Can I Afford? and Payment Estimator) without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. During these types of visits, we collect and store statistical information on an anonymous basis, such as the information about the time and length of your visit, the website you last visited, the pages you request, and the date and time of those requests. We may also collect and store the name of your Internet Service Provider. 

We use cookies when you enter our Site to help us gather this type of statistical information that does not include personally identifiable information. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive or device for record keeping purposes so that we can track Site, and user activity. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at most websites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, if you do so, some parts of the Site may not work properly for you. 

**5\. Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

Clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) help us better manage content on the Site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. 

We may also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. 

**6\. Log Files**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol(IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to track usersâ€™ movements around the Site and to improve our Site usability. 

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

**7\. Do Not Track Signals**

Our Site does not currently actively respond to "Do Not Track" browser signals or mechanisms. 

**8\. Your Privacy Choices**

If you are our customer, you may have certain privacy choices under applicable federal and state privacy laws. To update your sharing preferences please call, toll-free, 1-877-827-4884. Our menu will prompt you through your choices. 

**9\. Your Marketing Choices**

You may tell us about your preferences for receiving marketing materials from us as follows: 

  1. a. _Email/Text_ : To unsubscribe from any promotional email or text that we may send to you, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each such communication.
  2. b. _Internet_ : You can provide us with your marketing preferences when you log into your account by visiting the “My Profile” tab and clicking on “Email Alerts” and “Preferences.”

You will be able to update or change your preferences about receiving our marketing materials at any time. 

Please be aware that, even if you have opted out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still contact you for transactional purposes. Some examples are contacts for customer service, product information, service or reminder notices, or recalls. 

**10\. Accuracy of Your Information**

You may submit corrections or changes to your personally identifiable information by contacting us by: 

  1. a. _Phone_ : Toll-free 1-866-331-5632
  2. b. _Postal Mail_ : Kia Motors Finance, P.O. Box 20825, Fountain Valley, CA 92728-0825
  3. c. _Fax_ : (714) 965-0520

**11\. Confidentiality, Security, and Data Retention**

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you, including your social security number, to those employees and other persons hired by us who need to know the information to provide products and services to you and to otherwise service your account(s) with us. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

If you choose to complete and submit our Online Credit Application, or to access your Online Account Services through our Site, your personal information will be protected during transmission by an encryption process. 

We will retain your information in accordance with our data retention policy and schedule. 

**12\. Children's Privacy**

Our Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13), nor do we market products or services to such children. We request that children do not provide personal information through our Site. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 without parental consent. For more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), visit the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) website. 

**13\. Your California Privacy Rights **

We will not disclose any of your nonpublic personal information to our affiliates or to nonaffiliated financial companies who market or offer financial products or services under a joint marketing agreement with us, without first giving you notice and the opportunity to opt out. We also do not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to non-affiliates without first obtaining your express written consent, unless permitted by law. 

**14\. Your Vermont Privacy Rights**

We automatically limit the sharing of your information as if you elected to limit the sharing as described on page 1 of the [ Download Kia Motors Finance Customer Privacy Notice.](https://pfile.hcamerica.com/content/dam/hca/kmf/img/privacy-policy/2016-kmf-na-na-privacy_policy-pdf.PDF) With respect to sharing with nonaffiliated financial companies with whom we have joint marketing agreements, we limit the information to your name, contact information and information about your transactions and experiences with us. We also do not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to non-affiliates without first obtaining your express written consent, unless permitted by law. 

**15\. Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

As permitted by law, we may change this Privacy Policy. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy in the future, we will notify you through this Site. 

**16\. How to Contact Us**

We continuously strive to comply with all applicable federal and state privacy laws. You can contact our privacy office with any privacy related questions through the following: 

  1. a. _Phone_ : Toll-free 1-866-331-5632 
  2. b. _Email_ : [Privacy@hcamerica.com](mailto:Privacy@hcamerica.com)
  3. c. _Postal Mail_ : Privacy Department, 3161 Michelson Drive, Ste 1900, Irvine, CA 92612

**Effective Date of this Policy 1/1/14**
